COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
What's with you?!
Decisive Battle
on
the
Bridge!
Zabuza Returns!!
Good morning!
Here.
Thank you.
Naruto didn't come back
last night, either?
He's such a fool,
he's been out every night,
climbing trees.
He might be dead already
from using up too much Chakra.
I wonder if Naruto-kun's okay.
To think a child's out in
the middle of the night.
Well, you don't need to worry.
Although he may not seem to be,
he's a full-fledged Ninja.
I wonder...
That idiot's probably
all pooped out right about now.
Sasuke-kun?
I'm going for a walk.
But we're about to eat...
That was fast!
You'll catch a cold if
you keep sleeping here.
Who're you?
Uh... Did you wake me up, nee-chan?
I mean, what're you doing here?
I'm gathering medicinal herbs.
Herbs?
Yes. For healing injuries,
sickness and the like.
You got a lot to do early
in the morning, nee-chan...
You, too.
What've you been doing
in a place like this so early?
Training!
Could it be that...
you're a Ninja or something?
What with that headband and...
Is that what I look like? Is it?
Yup! I'm a Ninja!
No kidding.
You're great, aren't you.
But... why are you training?
As for me,
I want to get stronger!
But, you already look
strong enough.
No, no! I want to get
even stronger!
What for?
To become the best Ninja
in my village!
I'm going to get everyone
to recognize my strength!
And I have to prove something
to a certain person!
Is that for the sake of somebody?
Or is it for your own sake?
Huh?
What's so funny?!
Do you have somebody
precious in your life?
Precious...?
What is it you want to say, nee-chan?
What is it?
When a person has something
precious they want to protect...
that's when they can truly
become strong.
Your dad loves the town
you're from, so...
I absolutely won't allow
my comrades to get killed!
Get your hands off Iruka-sensei!
I'll kill you!!
Yeah! I know that well, too!
You'll get strong.
Yeah!
I hope we meet again somewhere.
Oh... and...
I'm a man!
That can't be!
He's cuter than Sakura-chan.
Why? That's strange.
This world is full of mystery...
Ouch.
Hey! What're you doing?!
Did you forget about mealtime,
you idiot?
Naruto?
What in the world is Naruto doing?
And Sasuke-kun hasn't come back
from his walk either...
No way...
Naruto can climb that high now?
Wow!
How 'bout that, how 'bout that?!
As for me,
I can climb this high now!
Whoa!
Oh, you idiot!
This is bad!
Gotcha!
You fell for it, you fell for it!
Don't scare us like that!
I'll kill him later! Shannaro!
He's grown a little, eh.
Oh! You idiot, Naruto!
It's cuz you went overboard!
You fool.
Sasuke...?
Nice, Sasuke-kun.
You're awesome!
These kids are really growing.
Uzumaki...
Naruto, eh.
You've recovered considerably.
All right...
Just a little more, Haku.
Yes.
Shall we go back?
Okay!
They're late.
And not just Naruto,
but even Sasuke-kun too.
What happened to you guys?
You're really muddy
and really wiped out.
We both... climbed up to the top.
Good.
Naruto, Sasuke, you'll also start guarding
Tazuna-san next time!
Got it! Whoa!
You idiot!
In just a teeny little bit,
the bridge will be complete.
It's thanks to you guys.
Even so, don't let your guard down...
I've really wanted to ask
you for a long time now...
But why are you still here
even though I lied about the mission?
To see what is right without doing it
bespeaks an absence of courage.
Like master, like man.
It's a teaching of the late Hokage.
The things I truly
hold dear to myself...
I'll protect until the very end
with both these arms.
Don't cry... Inari.
Why...?
What is it?
Why do you desperately work so hard
until you get like that?!
There's no way you'd be
a match for Gato's men even if you train!
No matter what cool things you say
or how much effort you make...
the weak always lose out...
against the truly strong!
Shut up. I'm not like you.
Shut up!
Looking at you makes me sick!
Sticking your nose in even though
you know nothing of this land!
I'm not like you who's always
acting frivolous
not knowing one thing about pain!
So you're just gonna cry
all day like the lead in a tragedy?
An idiot like you can just cry forever!
You crybaby!
Naruto! That's a bit harsh!
Naruto...
Got a minute?
Naruto didn't mean any harm
with what he said...
He's just uncouth, so...
We heard the story
about your father from Tazuna-san.
Like you, Naruto never had
a father as a young child...
Actually he doesn't know either
of his parents.
Not only that.
He didn't have a single friend.
What?
However...
I've never seen him sulk,
be timid, or cry.
He's always eager,
wanting to be acknowledged by someone.
If it's for the sake of that "dream,"
he always risks his life.
He's probably tired of crying.
So, he knows the true meaning
of the word strong.
Like your father.
Naruto might understand your feelings
the most.
What Naruto said earlier...
There's no mistaking that
he's told himself that over and over again.
Okay, then!
I leave Naruto in your hands.
Because he's used his body
to the limit...
I don't think he'll be able
to move today.
Kakashi-san, are you feeling all right?
Yes, somehow.
We'll be going!
What're you doing?
I didn't hire you guys for charity work...
Hey, are you listening, Zabuza?!
Hey!!
Shall we go... Haku?
Yes.
I overslept!
Hey hey!! Where is everyone?
Naruto-kun. Your Sensei wanted you
to rest and relax... today
I knew it.
They left me behind.
I'll be back.
Damn it!
They could've woken me up!
W-What the hell is this?!
What is going on?
What's happened?
It couldn't be...
Inari! Give me a hand.
Inari!?
I'll be right there.
This mist...
Sasuke! Sakura!
They're coming!
I knew he was still alive.
Making an appearance so soon, eh...
Say, Kakashi-sensei.
This is his... Hidden Mist Jutsu, right?!
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Kakashi.
I see you've got those brats
with you as always.
He's still trembling. Poor thing.
I'm trembling with... excitement.
Do it, Sasuke.
I can see it!
Well-well. So he could
see the Water Clones, eh.
That brat's grown quite a bit.
This means a rival has emerged, Haku.
So it seems.
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
Phew, that was a close shave.
Sorry I was late.
But Inari, you were great.
I was able to save your mom
thanks to your courage.
Hey, wait a minute.
Doesn't the fact that
we were attacked mean
that Kakashi-sensei and
the others are in danger too?!
Next episode:
"Haku's Master Technique. Mirror of Ice Crystals."
I'm going to kick butt once again!